A Guide to the Norman Sisisky Papers, 1982-2001
Library of Virginia
- Series VI. Speeches, 1983-2000., Extent: 14 boxes. (Box 77-90)
  - Floor Statements and Testimony - 1983. (Box 90, Folder 38)
  - Floor Statements and Testimony - 1984. (Box 90, Folder 39)
  - Floor Statements and Testimony - 1985. (Box 90, Folder 40)
  - Floor Statements and Testimony - 1986. (Box 90, Folder 41)
  - Floor Statements and Testimony - 1987. (Box 90, Folder 42)
- Series VII. Campaign Files, 1982-1996., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 91-93)
  Most of the campaign files relate to Sisisky's first run for Congress in 1982 against incumbent Robert Williams Daniel, Jr. Included are a briefing book, clippings, campaign staff list, information on Daniel's contributors, his legislative and voting record, and ratings, as well as Sisisky's record in the Virginia House of Delegates, and campaign projects and events. Also included in this series are reports and public opinion surveys prepared by the firm Hamilton and Staff of Washington, D.C. in response to Sisisky's contemplating a run for Virginia governor in 1989. There are also briefing books for his 1992, 1994, and 1996 congressional campaigns.
  Chronological by election year
  - Backups for Advertisements - 1982. (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Biographical - 1982. (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Briefing Book - 1982. (Box 91, Folder 3-5)
  - Campaign Staff List - 1982. (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Clippings - 1982. (Box 91, Folder 7-9)
  - Daniel, Robert Williams, Jr. - 1982. (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Daniel-FEC Information - 1979-1980. (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Daniel-Financial Research (Contributions) - 1982. (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Daniel-Legislation/Voting Record (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Daniel-Propoganda 1982. (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Daniel-Ratings (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Daniel-Record in Congress (Box 92, Folder 1-2)
  - Legislative Record - Virginia House of Delegates (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Projects/Events - 1982. (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Voting Locations/Precincts - 1982. (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Tabular Report - 1989. (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Data Presentation - 1989. (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Data Presentation - 1990. (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Data Presentation and Tabular Report - 1990. (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Survey Analysis - 1990. (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Tabular Report - 1990. (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Briefing Book - 1992. (Box 92, Folder 12-13)
  - Briefing Book-Small Business - 1992. (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Briefing Book - 1994. (Box 93, Folder 1-4)
  - Briefing Book - 1996. (Box 93, Folder 5-6)
- Series VIII. Miscellaneous Files, 1983-2001., Extent: 1 box. (Box 94)
  The miscellaneous files contain a compilation of Sisisky's congressional career by two members of his staff, miscellaneous memoranda and a staff directory, obituaries and condolences, and a visitors register covering the years 1993 to 2001.
  - "Legacy of Congressman Norman Sisisky, 1983-2001 - Compiled by Rick Franklin and Joan Fallon - (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Obituaries and Condolences - 2001. (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Staff Directory (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Staff Memos (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Visitors Register - 1993-2001. (Box 94, Folder 5)
- Series IX. Photographs, 1982-2000., Extent: 4 boxes. (Box 95-98)
  The photographs are arranged chronologically. They include images of Sisisky speaking at various events, photographs with constituents and colleagues, and of him on congressional trips. There is also a group of identified photographs with no date, and a group of unidentified images.
  - Democratic Luncheon for Incoming Freshmen - 1982. (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Douglas MacArthur Memorial Banquet, Norfolk - 22 January 1983. (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Aerospace Education Foundation Dinner - 15 June 1983. (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Emporia District Office - Small Business Advisory Task Force - 6 July 1983. (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Isle of Wight Citizens Association Fair and Fundraiser - August 1983. (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Democratic New Members' Caucus Dinner - 20 September 1983. (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Price, Mel; Sisisky; Zablocki, Clement - 1983. (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Virginia State Sheriff's Association 50th Anniversary Conference- 1983. (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Virginia State Sheriff's Association Luncheon - 1983. (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Sisisky's Washington Staff - 1983. (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - American Legion Conference - 28 February 1984. (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Company - 21 March 1984. (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - House Armed Services Committee - 2 October 1983. (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Democratic National Convention - 1984. (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - First Annual Seafood Feast, Isle of Wight County - 1984. (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - USS Tarawa Visit - 1984. (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Safeway "C" Flag Presentation - January 1985. (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - National Security Leadership Award - April 1985. (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - General John Galvin Luncheon - 25 July 1985. (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - House Select Committee on Aging - 30 July 1985. (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Social Security Anniversary Celebration - August 1985. (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - "Buy American" Procurement Mission with Taiwan - 22 October 1985. (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - Portsmouth Moose Lodge Open Season Insurance Seminar - 9 November 1985. (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - Joint Session of Congress Following Geneva Summit - 21 November 1985. (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - Grumman, Long Island, NY - 1985. (Box 95, Folder 25)
  - Norfolk Naval Shipyard Refuse Derived Fuel Power Plant - 1985. (Box 95, Folder 26)
  - Rural Homesteading Program, Lawrenceville - 1985. (Box 95, Folder 27)
  - Ship "Eagle" Arrival, Hampton Roads - 1985. (Box 95, Folder 28)
  - National Sheriff's Association - February 1986. (Box 95, Folder 29)
  - USS Newport News Launching - 15 March 1986. (Box 95, Folder 30)
  - National Security Leadership Award - 16 July 1986. (Box 95, Folder 31)
  - McGee, Robert; Sisisky; Morris, Denny; Rhyner, Roger - 1986. (Box 95, Folder 32)
  - Ship "Elissa" Visit - 1986. (Box 95, Folder 33)
  - Turner, Carmen E. - 1986. (Box 95, Folder 34)
  - Army Logistics Management Center Groundbreaking, Fort Lee - 6 April 1987. (Box 95, Folder 35)
  - National Security Leadership Award - 14 October 1987. (Box 95, Folder 36)
  - Coehlo, Tony - 1987. (Box 95, Folder 37)
  - Navy Summer Pageant and Reception - 1987. (Box 95, Folder 38)
  - Pickett, Owen B. - 1987. (Box 95, Folder 39)
  - USS Theodore Roosevelt Visit - 1987. (Box 95, Folder 40)
  - Wright, Sara; Barlow, Gladys - 1987. (Box 95, Folder 41)
  - Beaham, Gordon T. III; Sisisky - "Golden Bulldog Award" - 22 September 1988. (Box 95, Folder 42)
  - Small Business Subcommittee on Exports, Tax Policy, and Special Problems - 11 October 1989. (Box 95, Folder 43)
  - Morocco Trip - 1989. (Box 95, Folder 44)
  - Sisisky; Womack, Marvin - "Golden Bulldog Award" - 28 February 1990. (Box 95, Folder 45)
  - IMPAC 2000 Reception - 6 March 1990. (Box 95, Folder 46)
  - Glickman, Dan - Secretary of Agriculture - VSU Field Day - 22 March 1990. (Box 95, Folder 47)
  - New Prison Announcement, Prince George County - 15 April 1990. (Box 95, Folder 48)
  - Ritchie, John - VHDA Executive Director, Portsmouth - June 1990. (Box 95, Folder 49)
  - Stone Container Corporation, Hopewell - 21 August 1990. (Box 95, Folder 50)
  - "Eagle of Freedom" Award - 1990. (Box 95, Folder 51)
  - Graves, Earl; Sisisky; Johnson, Earvin "Magic" - 1990. (Box 95, Folder 52)
  - Presidential Classroom Students Visit - 29 January 1991. (Box 95, Folder 53)
  - Joint Session of Congress - End of First Gulf War - March 1991. (Box 95, Folder 54)
  - International Military Students at Fort Lee Visit - 20 June 1991. (Box 95, Folder 55)
  - Great Dismal Swamp National Wildlife Refuge Dedication - 28 September 1991. (Box 95, Folder 56)
  - Procurement Assistance Meeting, Fort Lee - 23 March 1992. (Box 95, Folder 57)
  - Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Company - 16 April 1992. (Box 95, Folder 58)
  - Rowe, Michael; Sisisky - 24 June 1992. (Box 95, Folder 59)
  - Sisisky; Lowery, Kristin - July 1992. (Box 95, Folder 60)
  - Norfolk Naval Shipyard Ship Services Support Facility Groundbreaking - 11 December 1992. (Box 95, Folder 61)
  - Cuomo, Mario - 1992. (Box 95, Folder 62)
  - Food Distribution Industry "Thomas Jefferson Award" - 1992. (Box 95, Folder 63)
  - Martin, Lynn - Secretary of Labor - 1992. (Box 95, Folder 64)
  - Sisisky; Bobby Scott; Stanley Walker - President-Elect Clinton's Visit to Richmond - 1992. (Box 95, Folder 65)
  - Reserve Officers Association Congressional Luncheon - 27 January 1993. (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Aspin, Les - Secretary of Defense Swearing-In - 1 February 1993. (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Richards, Ann - Congressional Sunbelt Caucus Luncheon - 12 February 1993. (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Planter's Peanuts Plant Groundbreaking, Suffolk - 15 April 1993. (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Base Realignment and Closure Commission - 10 June 1993. (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Shad Planking - 1993. (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Acute Care Facility Groundbreaking, Naval Medical Center, Portsmouth - 28 February 1994. (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Collegiate School Group - March 1994. (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Grumman - September 1994. (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Joint Armed Services Holiday Reception - December 1994. (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Farmers Advisory Board - 1994. (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - EDO Ribbon-Cutting Ceremony, Chesapeake - 20 April 1995. (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Cornella, Alton W.; Sisisky - 16 June 1995. (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Hampton - 1 December 1995. (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - French Embassy Dinner - 1995. (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - WWII 50th Anniversary Ceremony, National Archives - 1995. (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Grizzard, Mary Beth - 1996. (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Maisel, Kevin - 9 April 1997. (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - Old Dominion University Commencement - 10 May 1997. (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - New Ferry Stop, High Street Landing - 10 July 1997. (Box 96, Folder 21)
  - Sperling, Stuart - 29 July 1997. (Box 96, Folder 22)
  - Bain, Billy; Sisisky; Cotton, Dell - Peanut Growers Cooperative Marketing Association - August 1997. (Box 96, Folder 23)
  - Robert K. Guest Retirement Dinner, Fort Lee - August 1997. (Box 96, Folder 24)
  - Craig, John - Air Force Association Convention - 16 September 1997. (Box 96, Folder 25)
  - Southside Regional Medical Center - School of Nursing Visit to Washington, DC - 8 October 1997. (Box 96, Folder 26)
  - Jack Brooks Portrait Unveiling - 19 October 1997. (Box 96, Folder 27)
  - Carter G. Woodson Elementary School Visit to Washington, D.C. - 30 October 1997. (Box 96, Folder 28)
  - One Stop Center Opening - 5 December 1997. (Box 96, Folder 29)
  - Shelton, Henry Hugh; Sisisky - 19 October 1997. (Box 96, Folder 30)
  - Harrison Villas, Fort Lee - 26 January 1998. (Box 96, Folder 31)
  - Stonebridge Middle School Visit to Washington, D.C. - 28 April 1998. (Box 96, Folder 32)
  - Cohen, William S. - Secretary of Defense Visit to Norfolk State University - May 1998. (Box 96, Folder 33)
  - Small Business of the Year Award, Chesapeake - 8 June 1998. (Box 96, Folder 34)
  - Southside Electrical Cooperative Visit to Washington, D.C. - June 1998. (Box 96, Folder 35)
  - Johnson, Nicole (Miss Virginia); Sisisky - July 1998. (Box 96, Folder 36)
  - Southampton Academy Visit to Washington, D.C. - 28 September 1998. (Box 96, Folder 37)
  - Norfolk Naval Shipyard, Portsmouth Association - 10 December 1998. (Box 96, Folder 38)
  - Consumer Housing Fair, Chesapeake - 8 May 1999. (Box 96, Folder 39)
  - Moore Middle School Visit to Washington, D.C. - 26 May 1999. (Box 96, Folder 40)
  - Emporia Visitors Center/ISTEA Project Ribbon Cutting - August 1999. (Box 96, Folder 41)
  - Defense Commissary Agency Addition - 8 September 1999. (Box 96, Folder 42)
  - Portsmouth Memorial Day Parade - 1999. (Box 96, Folder 43)
  - Western Barbecue, Chief of Naval Operations - 9 June 1999. (Box 96, Folder 44)
  - South Norfolk Civic League Parade - 4 July 1999. (Box 96, Folder 45)
  - Washington Park - July 1999 8 May 1999. (Box 96, Folder 46)
  - Nstional Defense University Capstone Course - October 1999. (Box 96, Folder 47)
  - Great Bridge Bridge/Elizabeth River Project Boat Ride - November 1999. (Box 96, Folder 48)
  - Downtown Franklin Opening - 1 December 1999. (Box 96, Folder 49)
  - Smurfit-Stone Container, Hopewell - 8 December 1999. (Box 96, Folder 50)
  - Camp Holly, Chester - 1999. (Box 96, Folder 51)
  - Korea Trip - 1999. (Box 96, Folder 52)
  - Peanut Growers Association - 1999. (Box 96, Folder 53)
  - Petersburg Relay for Life - 1999. (Box 96, Folder 54)
  - UVA University Democrats Visit - 1999. (Box 96, Folder 55)
  - "Distinguished Friend of Virginia Agriculture" Award - 13 January 2000. (Box 96, Folder 56)
  - Virginia Congressional Delegation, Governor's Mansion, Richmond - February 2000. (Box 96, Folder 57)
  - USDA Rural Development Conference, Franklin - 12 February 2000. (Box 96, Folder 58)
  - "Local Legacies" - Library of Congress - 24 May 2000. (Box 96, Folder 59)
  - Floyd Spence Portrait Dedication - 25 September 2000. (Box 96, Folder 60)
  - Sobol, Faye; Askew, Janel and Hazel; Sisisky - 27 October 2000. (Box 96, Folder 61)
  - U.S. Chamber of Commerce "Spirit of Enterprise" Award - 2000. (Box 96, Folder 62)
  - AARP Luncheon - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - "American Values" Annual Award Dinner, Chesapeake (John Conyers) - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Les Aspin - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Bennett, Charles - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Bowersox, Kenneth D. - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Bush, George H.W. - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Chesterfield Chamber of Commerce - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - The Children's Place - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Colonial Heights Kiwanis Club - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Crater Small Business Development Center - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Davis, Sareese - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Duggins, George C.; Sisisky - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Emporia District Office Ribbon Cutting - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Gilmore, James S. III; Sisisky - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Greenfield, Wilbert - VSU President - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Sisisky; Harman, Jane F. - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Harris, Karen - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - James Madison Memorial Fellowship Foundation - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Lake View Technology Center Groundbreaking - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - National Guard Armory Groundbreaking, Emporia - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 20)
  - Natter, Bob - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 21)
  - Norfolk Naval Shipyard, Portsmouth Association - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 22)
  - Oman, Sidney M.; Sisisky; Jennings, J. Bennie - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 23)
  - Peacock, Tiffany Alisa - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 24)
  - Schwarzkopf, Norman - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Sisisky; Friedrich, Ingo; Watson, Tom - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 26)
  - Sisisky; Hurley, Ed - Amelia County - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 27)
  - Sisisky; Milligan, Norman - American Subcontracting Association Award - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 28)
  - Sisisky, Norman - WWII Navy - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 29)
  - USS Alabama Visit - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 30)
  - USS Iowa Visit - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 31)
  - USS Portsmouth - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 32)
  - Sisisky; Wrenn, Ashley - n.d.. (Box 97, Folder 33)
  - Award Presentations - n.d.. (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Constituents - n.d.. (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Events - n.d.. (Box 98, Folder 3-12)
  - School Groups - n.d.. (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Sisisky Attending Committee Hearings n.d.. (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Sisisky Portraits n.d.. (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Photograph Documentation - n.d.. (Box 98, Folder 16)
- Series X. Special Media, 1982-2001., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 99-101)
  The special media includes videtapes of Sisisky on local and national news programs and talk shows, local news coverage of issues affecting his district, campaign debates, and House floor debates. There are videotapes of local reaction to Sisisky's death, and coverage of his colleages tributes on the floor of the House. This series also contains cassette tape recordings of appearances by him at local events, reel to reel recordings of public service announcements, and computer floppy discs of staff memoranda and other files.
  - Videotape - Sisisky Receiving Gavel at Subcommittee Hearing on Child Care - 8 June 1988.
  - Videotape - News Report on Export 89, American-European Small Business Trade Congress - held in Frankfort on 25-29 October 1989 (includes Sisisky remarks) - 24 July 1989.
  - Videotape - Spot for 1990 Census.
  - Videotape - Channel 3 Local News Coverage of Iraq Force Resolution; WVEC Channel 13 coverage of Arab reaction in Tidewater area, activation of Navy Reserve units, Navy Secretary visit, Congressional debate (Sisisky interview) - 1990.
  - Videotape - Inside Edition re: infomercials; McNeil/Lehrer; Wall Street Journal; Today Show; Good Morning America; CBS This Morning - 1990.
  - Videotape - "Watch on Washington"-Trade - February 1990.
  - Videotape - CNBC "Media Beat" Infomercials Segment - 8 February 1990.
  - Videotape - CBS This Morning - 23 August 1990.
  - Videotape - McLaughlin Group - NS by phone re: infomercials - 19 December 1990.
  - Videotape - Norman Schwarzkopf Briefing, Kuwait Rebuilding Briefing - 1991.
  - Videotape - Channel 13 Interview re: Persian Gulf; Joel Rubin Interview; Sisisky and Jack Dorsey, Persian Gulf and Defense Budget - February 1991.
  - Videotape - Housing Conference, Suffolk (Two Copies) - 1991.
  - Videotape - USS Iowa/Clayton Hartwig Investigation; Chesapeake Expressway/Wetlands Impact - 1991.
  - Videotape - Lake Gaston Hearing - 13 June 1992.
  - Videotape - Sisisky-Zevgolis Debate - 11 October 1992.
  - Videotape - WVEC-13 Hampton Roads "On the Record" Debate between Sisisky and Zevgolis - 1992.
  - Videotape - Joel Rubin Show - 1 November 1992.
  - Videotape - City Council Meeting - 18 May 1993.
  - Videotape - BRAC Commission Hearings on Norfolk Naval Shipyard - 11 June 1993.
  - Videotape - BRAC Hearing - Chrysler Hall, Norfolk - 11 June 1993.
  - Videotape - Washington Week in Review G7 Summit Coverage; Wall Street Week; WAVY-10 News - Coverage of Naval Undersea Warfare Center Closing/Move-BRAC - July 1993.
  - Videotape - Sisisky Holiday Public Service Announcement - 30 seconds (2 VHS copies and 3 V-MATIC copies) - 8 December 1993.
  - Videotape - "Coping with Colorectal Cancer and the Importance of Early Detection" - 1994.
  - Videotape - Health Care Forum, City Council Chambers, Chesapeake - 31 March 1994.
  - Videotape - WCTV-23 Chesapeake "Newsbreak" - 17 May 1994.
  - Videotape - Investiture Ceremony, Suffolk City Council Chambers - 1 July 1994.
  - Videotape - WTVR-3 Norfolk Route 168 Report-Sisisky/Sweet Appearance - 1994.
  - Videotape - WCTV-48 "Sounding Board" - 3 October 1994.
  - Videotape - WTVR-3 Norfolk Coverage of Sisisky/Sweet Debate - 24 October 1994.
  - Videotape - Questions in National Security Committee - Secretary Perry - February 1995.
  - Videotape - Shrum/Devine Medicare Informational Video - 25 May 1995.
  - Videotape - Sisisky Birthday Roast, Suffolk Democratic Committee, Suffolk National Guard Armory - 10 June 1995.
  - Videotape - House Floor Coverage - 1 August 1995.
  - Videotape - "Keeping America's Dream Alive - Dane Strother for the DCCC" - 29 February 1996.
  - Videotape - WGOV-48 Portsmouth "Meet the Congressman" - 5 March 1996.
  - Videotape - WVEC-TV Norfolk "It's Your Time" - 27 October 1996.
  - Videotape - Fort Pickett Change of Command - 30 September 1997.
  - Videotape - WAVY Live - 20 August 1998.
  - Videotape - Joel Rubin Show - 23 August 1998.
  - Videotape - WCTV-48 "Sounding Board" - 1 November 1998.
  - Videotape - CNN Late Edition with Wolf Blitzer in Jerusalem - Interview with Sisisky re: impeachment - 1998.
  - Videotape - House Floor Debate on HR 612 to show support for troops in the Persian Gulf (includes Sisisky remarks) - 17 December 1998.
  - Videotape - Today Show - 19 April 1998.
  - Videotape - Portsmouth Naval Hospital - 30 April 1998.
  - Videotape - WCTV-48 "Sounding Board" - 6 June 1998.
  - Videotape - WHRO-15 "Washington Week in Review"; "Wall Street Week"; "This Week in Hampton Roads" with report on EPA Superfund Washington Park site and others - 1999.
  - Videotape - WCTV-48 "Sounding Board" - 5 March 2000.
  - Videotape - House Floor Coverage re: USS Cole Attack incl. Sisisky comments - October 2000.
  - Videotape - Tribute in Memory of NS, House Floor (Two Copies) - 29 March 2001.
  - Videotape - Marriage Penalty Floor Debate with announcement of death of Sisisky - 29 March 2001.
  - Videotape - House Floor Tribute to NS, incl. comments by Richard Gephardt, Saxby Chambliss, John Spratt, Roy Blunt, Ciro Rodriguez, Porter Goss, Charles Stenholm, James Moran, Frank Wolf - 29 March 2001.
  - Videotape - WCTV-48 "Chesapeake This Week" Coverage of Sisisky's Death, Sid Oman Tribute, and City Council Resolution in Sisisky's Honor (5 copies) - 2001.
  - Videotape - BRAC Commission re: Army Corps - n.d..
  - Videotape - BRAC Hearing - Naval Undersea Warfare Center - n.d..
  - Videotape - CSPAN BRAC - Adding Fort Lee, Fort Monroe, Norfolk Naval Shipyard, Oceana, etc. - n.d..
  - Videotape - Naval Undersea Warfare Center and BRAC Decision Process, Local News Coverage - n.d..
  - Videotape - Channel 13 "On the Record" Base Closings interviews with Reps. Scott, Bateman, and Sisisky - n.d..
  - Videotape - Hampton Roads and the Base Closure Process, Hampton Roads Planning District Commission - n.d..
  - Videotape - Today Show - Sisisky on Navy budget cuts - n.d..
  - Videotape - Today Show - Rep. Gray - n.d..
  - Videotape - Washington Park, Channel 13 - n.d..
  - Videotape - "Battlefield Boulevard: A Road Under Siege" - n.d..
  - Videotape - PBS "American Interests"; Miscellaneous; WHRO (Local PBS) re: defense and Hampton Roads economy - n.d..
  - Videotape - DCCC Medicare Anniversary - n.d..
  - Videotape - "Fighting For Medicare" - n.d..
  - Videotape - "The US Congress and You" sponsored by the John Randolph Medical Center - n.d..
  - Videotape - "This Week in Hampton Roads" Health Care in the Tidewater Area including an interview with Sisisky re: cancer diagnosis, screening, treatment, etc. - n.d..
  - Videotape - House Floor Debate on National Defense Authorization Act Amendments (No Appearance by Sisisky)- n.d..
  - Cassette Tape - National Infomercial Marketing Association Annual Conference (Four Copies) - 22-23 October 1990.
  - Cassette Tape - Health Care Town Meeting (Two Copies) - 14 January 1992.
  - Cassette Tape - Emporia Rotary Club - 5 July 1994.
  - Cassette Tape - Sid Oman Cancer Treatment Center Dedication, WFOS Broadcast - 26 April 1998.
  - Cassette Tape - "Vantage Point" - 1 June 1999.
  - Cassette Tape - Census Public Service Announcement, Sisisky/Pickett - 2000.
  - Cassette Tape - "Vantage Point" WFOS Tribute with Sidney Oman (Two Copies) - 2 April 2001.
  - Floppy Disk - Floyd Mail Index/Sisisky Mail Codes/Archive Notes (Two Copies).
  - Floppy Disk - Floyd Files/Defense Issues (Two Copies).
  - Floppy Disk - Floyd Files/Domestic Issues, International Relations (Two Copies).
  - Floppy Disk - Sisisky Floyd Files/Navy Issues (Two Copies).
  - Floppy Disk - CP 968-1089.
  - Floppy Disk - CP 1090-1195.
  - Floppy Disk - CP 1196-1296.
  - Floppy Disk - CP 1297-1460.
  - Floppy Disk - CP 1461-1599.
  - Floppy Disk - CP 1600-1712.
  - Floppy Disk - CP 1823-1943.
  - Floppy Disk - Chris 1944-2067 Issues File.
  - Floppy Disk - CP 2068-2204.
  - Floppy Disk - CP 2335-2475.
  - Floppy Disk - CP 2476.
  - Floppy Disk - Robo Language.
  - Floppy Disk - Eliza/Robo Responses.
  - Floppy Disk - AFTC Letter/VCU/MCV.
  - Floppy Disk - Spring 2001 Newsletter.
  - Floppy Disk - Miscellaneous Files.